HANNA TISCHER

hannalt@live.unc.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/hanna-leth-tischer

hannalt.github.io

704-928-7887

About

Hanna Tischer is a thoughtful, ambitious, and creative Tech Specialist with professional

Leadership Experience. Her technical skills are backed by her unique ability to communicate them.

This has allowed her to continually lead teams to out-perform their goals.

Education

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Expected May 2022

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) in Computer Science

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in English, concentration in Creative Writing

GPA: 3.681

Honors

Honors Carolina - Highly competitive, four-year academic program enrolling 10% of each class **Buckley Public Service Scholar** - Four-year fellowship focused on community service **UNC Dean's List** - Spring 2019, Fall 2019, Qualified - Spring 2020, Fall 2020, Spring 2021

Professional Experience

General Electric Gas Power

Atlanta, GA

Digital Technology Intern

May 2021 – August 2021

- Used Tableau to create Operations Dashboards to standardize the definition of application success across GE Gas Power.
- Created an automatic NLP classification for application incidents, changes, and requests. Increasing the efficiency of ticket and application problem identification.
- Created an Automatic Application Verifier to quickly and on request check the web statuses of critical apps during vulnerable events.
- Worked with a GE GRC Team to use a Zero-Shot BART Model to make a binary decision on information requests.

Department of Computer Science, UNC

Chapel Hill, NC

Research Assistant

August 2020 – Present

- Used Natural Language Processing models to research sustainability and social good applications.
- Integrated knowledge with social media datasets to be used in the training of models.
- Participated in a weekly undergraduate reading group focusing on current Computer Science Research.

Department of Computer Science, UNC

Chapel Hill, NC

Teaching Assistant

January 2020 – Present

- Organized a team of twelve other Teaching Assistants to create curriculum for class.
- Conducted interviews for and trained new TAs.
- Held classes and office hours for ~200 students each semester.
- Graded homework, programming assignments, exams and hardware labs.

Ruffalo Noel Levitz, LLC at the UNC Engagement Center

Chapel Hill, NC

Shift Supervisor, former Development Representative

January 2019 – August 2020

- Oversaw the collection of \$785,000 worth of donations while managing a team of \sim 25 employees.
- Conducted interviews for and trained / onboarded new employees.
- As a Development Representative, raised \$50,000 by calling UNC alumni and parents.

Skills

Language Skills: Spanish (Intermediate), Danish (Basic)

Computer Skills: Java, C/C++, Python, Html/CSS, TypeScript, Swift, Git/GitHub, Linux/Unix, Vim, MatLab, Microsoft Office Suites, Tableau/Tableau Databases/Servers